<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HuaweiKitSampleApp</string>
    <string name="link"><u>Link to Official Website</u></string>
    <string name="csgo_about">Counter-Strike: Global Offensive (CS: GO) expands upon the team-based action gameplay that it pioneered when it was launched 19 years ago. \n\nCS: GO features new maps, characters, weapons, and game modes, and delivers updated versions of the classic CS content (de_dust2, etc.). \n\n\"Counter-Strike took the gaming industry by surprise when the unlikely MOD became the most played online PC action game in the world almost immediately after its release in August 1999\", said Doug Lombardi at Valve. \"For the past 12 years, it has continued to be one of the most-played games in the world, headline competitive gaming tournaments and selling over 25 million units worldwide across the franchise. CS: GO promises to expand on CS\' award-winning gameplay and deliver it to gamers on the PC as well as the next gen consoles and the Mac.\"</string>
    <string name="valorant_about">Valorant is a team-based first-person hero shooter set in the near future. Players play as one of a set of agents, characters designed based on several countries and cultures around the world. In the main game mode, players are assigned to either the attacking or defending team with each team having five players on it. Agents have unique abilities, each requiring charges, as well as a unique ultimate ability that requires charging through kills, deaths, orbs, or spike actions. \n\nEvery player starts each round with a "classic" pistol and one or more "signature ability" charges. Other weapons and ability charges can be purchased using an in-game economic system that awards money based on the outcome of the previous round, any kills the player is responsible for, and any actions taken with the spike. \n\nThe game has an assortment of weapons including secondary guns like sidearms and primary guns like submachine guns, shotguns, machine guns, assault rifles and sniper rifles. There are automatic and semi-automatic weapons that each have a unique shooting pattern that has to be controlled by the player to be able to shoot accurately. \n\nDifferent agents allow players to find more ways to plant the Spike and style on enemies with scrappers, strategists, and hunters of every description. It currently offers 16 agents to choose from. They are Brimstone, Viper, Omen, Cypher, Sova, Sage, Phoenix, Jett, Raze, Breach, Reyna, Killjoy, Skye, Yoru, Astra, and KAY/O.</string>
    <string name="dbd_about">Dead by Daylight is a multiplayer (4vs1) horror game where one player takes on the role of the savage Killer, and the other four players play as Survivors, trying to escape the Killer and avoid being caught, tortured and killed. \n\nSurvivors play in third-person and have the advantage of better situational awareness. The Killer plays in first-person and is more focused on their prey. \n\nThe Survivors\' goal in each encounter is to escape the Killing Ground without getting caught by the Killer - something that sounds easier than it is, especially when the environment changes every time you play.</string>
    <string name="genshin_about">Genshin Impact is an action role-playing game developed and published by Chinese game house miHoYo. It was released for Microsoft Windows, PlayStation 4, Android, and iOS in September 2020, for PlayStation 5 in April 2021, and, as of September 2021, is planned for future release on Nintendo Switch. \n\nGenshin Impact takes place in the fantasy world of Teyvat, which is home to seven distinct nations, each of which is tied to an element and ruled by a god associated with it. The story follows a twin, referred to as the Traveler (with the gender chosen by the player), who has traveled across many other worlds but has become separated from their twin sibling (of the opposite gender) in Teyvat. The Traveler travels in search of their lost sibling with their companion Paimon, and becomes involved in the affairs of Teyvat\'s nations and gods.</string>
    <string name="maple_about">MapleStory (Korean: 메이플스토리; RR: Meipeul Seutori) is a free-to-play, 2D, side-scrolling massively multiplayer online role-playing game, developed by South Korean company Wizet. Several versions of the game are available for specific countries or regions, and each is published by various companies such as Nexon. \n\nIn the game, players travel the "Maple World", defeating monsters and developing their characters\' skills and abilities as is typical in role-playing games. Players can interact with others in many ways, including chatting and trading. Groups of players can band together in parties to hunt monsters and share rewards, and can also form guilds to interact more easily with each other. Players additionally have the option to visit the in-game "Cash Shop" to purchase a variety of character appearances or gameplay enhancements with real money.</string>
    <string name="dragonest_about">Dragon Nest (Korean: 드래곤네스트) is a free-to-play fantasy MMORPG developed by Eyedentity and currently available in different regions and languages. Aside from boasting a non-targeting combat and skill system within instance dungeons, Dragon Nest also revolves around a rich story which is told in different points of view depending on the player\'s chosen class. \n\nDragon Nest receives new content, balance patches and cash shop items on a monthly basis. Major expansions that include several new dungeons, Nests, new classes, multiple new features or remake of old ones, extensive class adjustments and a raise on the level cap take place every year.</string>
    <string name="gta5_about">Grand Theft Auto V is a 2013 action-adventure game developed by Rockstar North and published by Rockstar Games. It is the seventh main entry in the Grand Theft Auto series, following 2008\'s Grand Theft Auto IV, and the fifteenth instalment overall. Set within the fictional state of San Andreas, based on Southern California, the single-player story follows three protagonists—retired bank robber Michael De Santa, street gangster Franklin Clinton, and drug dealer and gunrunner Trevor Philips—and their attempts to commit heists while under pressure from a corrupt government agency and powerful criminals. The open world design lets players freely roam San Andreas\' open countryside and the fictional city of Los Santos, based on Los Angeles. \n\nThe game is played from either a third-person or first-person perspective, and its world is navigated on foot and by vehicle. Players control the three lead protagonists throughout single-player and switch among them, both during and outside missions. The story is centred on the heist sequences, and many missions involve shooting and driving gameplay.</string>
    <string name="l4d_about">From Valve (the creators of Counter-Strike, Half-Life and more) comes Left 4 Dead, a co-op action horror game for the PC and Xbox 360 that casts up to four players in an epic struggle for survival against swarming zombie hordes and terrifying mutant monsters. \n\nSet in the immediate aftermath of the zombie apocalypse, L4D\'s survival co-op mode lets you blast a path through the infected in four unique “movies,” guiding your survivors across the rooftops of an abandoned metropolis, through rural ghost towns and pitch-black forests in your quest to escape a devastated Ground Zero crawling with infected enemies. Each "movie" is comprised of five large maps, and can be played by one to four human players, with an emphasis on team-based strategy and objectives.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string-array name="item1">
        <item>Building a good team for some wins!</item>
        <item>No Rank Limit Required.</item>
        <item>Playing Ranked Match. Need a Pro!</item>
        <item>Just for fun! Let\'s become Friends!</item>
        <item>Need Some Girl Players!</item>
        <item>Need Some Boy Players!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="item2">
        <item>-</item>
        <item>Mayday! Mayday! My friend list is EMPTY!</item>
        <item>Forever Alone (or might not\?)</item>
        <item>You don\'t have friend, so Come and Join us!</item>
        <item>Whatever.</item>
        <item>I will carry you.</item>
        <item>I need carry.</item>
        <item>Now or Never!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="item3">
        <item>-</item>
        <item>Gamer for life! Play everyday!</item>
        <item>Morning Gamer!</item>
        <item>Afternoon Gamer!</item>
        <item>Night Gamer!</item>
        <item>Midnight Gamer!</item>
        <item>Weekend Gamer!</item>
        <item>Weekdays Gamer!</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>